[{"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " so, i&#146;m in my apartment doing the soap opera digest crossword puzzle, and guess who the clue is for three down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  three down, days of our lives star blank tribbiani. that&#146;s me!! i&#146;m blank!!", "answer": " how cool is this?! we know three down! i&#146;m touching three down!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yeah you are baby.", "answer": " three down knows i&#146;m married, what&#146;s three down doin&#146;?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " so did they call you to tell you your name&#146;s gonna be in this?", "answer": " no. they really like me over there. they want to do a big profile on me, but i said no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " why&#146;d you say no?", "answer": " remember what happened the last time i did an interview for them? i said i write a lot of my own lines, and then the writers got mad and made my character fall down the elevator shaft. so who knows what i might say this time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh, come on joey! you will totally keep it in check this time, and plus y&#146;know the publicity would be really good for your career! and you deserve that! and if you do the interview you can mention, oh i don&#146;t know, gal pal rachel green?", "answer": " is that gal pal spelled l-o-s-e-r?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " okay, don&#146;t listen to him. please?", "answer": " fine! all right, i&#146;ll do it. but hey! you guys have to be at the next table so you can stop me if i y&#146;know, start to say something stupid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " just then or-or all the time, &#145;cause we-we have jobs y&#146;know.", "answer": " come on! we will be there for you the whole time! just remember gal pal rachel green.  ha-ha! i&#146;m gonna be in soap opera digest! and not just in the dumb crossword puzzle.  seriously, proud of you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " i really appreciate you taking the time to do this.", "answer": " oh, not at all. happy to do it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  you think we&#146;re being obvious?", "answer": " no, we&#146;re just four people with neck problems. you talk like this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": "  y&#146;know i think its great you wanted to meet here. y&#146;know when most people hear the magazine is paying for it they want to go to a big fancy restaurant.", "answer": "  actually, i didn&#146;t know the magazine was paying for it. wouldn&#146;t have mattered, i&#146;m doing this for the fans, not for the free food.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " can i get you anything?", "answer": " umm, i&#146;ll have a cup of coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " shhh! we&#146;re not talking.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " folks, has this ever happened to you. you go to the refrigerator to get a nice glass of milk,  and these darn cartons are so flingin'-flangin' hard to open.", "answer": " oh, you said it mike.  aw! there's got to be a better way!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " this is the first time he&#146;s ever used this product, he's never used this product before, you're gonna see how easy this is to do.  go ahead.  this works with any milk carton.", "answer": "  wow, it is easy.  now, i can have milk everyday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " so this is it? victor?", "answer": " yeah, i guess it is. and so&#133; i&#146;m gonna get on this spaceship,  and i&#146;m gonna go to blargon 7 in search of alternative fuels. but when i return, 200 years from now, you&#146;ll be long gone. but i won&#146;t have aged at all.  so you tell your great-great-granddaughter to look me up, because adrienne&#133; baby&#133;i&#146;m gonna want to meet her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " shh, ok, here i come, here i come. see i'm comin' to fix the copier, i can't get to the copier, i'm thinkin' what do i do, what do i do&#133;so i just watch 'em have sex. and then i say, wait, here's my line,  you know that's bad for the paper tray.", "answer": " nice work my friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " i&#146;m gonna get some coffee, anyone want anything?", "answer": " oh yeah, i&#146;d actually love a blueberry muffin and a chamomile tea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " uh, double latte, extra foam.", "answer": " and a bagel with only&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  look at this clown! just because he&#146;s got a bigger boat he thinks he can take up the whole river.  get out of the way jackass!  who names their boat coast guard anyway?", "answer": " that is the coast guard.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! check it out! this is unbelievable! joey has been holding his breath for almost four minutes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " well, i see you've had a very productive day. don't you think the cowboy hat is a little much?", "answer": "  come on, it's fun!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " all right!  isn't this a woman's hat?", "answer": " dude, stop talking crazy and make us some tea!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " y&#146;know what, we have to turn off the porn.", "answer": " i think you&#146;re right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " all right, ready?", "answer": " one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " two.", "answer": " three.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " that&#146;s kinda nice.", "answer": " yeah, that&#146;s kinda a relief.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " you wanna see if we still have it?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " free porn!!!", "answer": " yeah!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " a mento&#133;", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " like the candy?", "answer": " matter of fact, i do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " well umm, another thing our readers always want to know is how our soap stars stay in such great shape. do you have some kind of fitness regime?", "answer": " uh, we stars just try to eat right and get lots of exercise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " wow! you realize that we've been throwing this ball, without dropping it, for like an hour?", "answer": " are you serious?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " yeah. i realized it about a half-hour ago but i didn't want to say anything 'cause i didn't want to jinx it.", "answer": " wow! we are pretty good at this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " hey! we totally forgot about lunch!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " what&#146;s wrong with you?", "answer": " nothing! well, i-i got this blinding pain in my stomach when i was lifting weights before, then i uh passed out and uh, haven&#146;t been able to stand up since. but um, i don&#146;t think it&#146;s anything serious.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " this sounds like a hernia. you have to&#151;you-you&#151;go to the doctor!", "answer": " no way! &#145;kay look, if i have to go to the doctor for anything it&#146;s gonna be for this thing sticking out of my stomach!  why did i have to start working out again?  damn you 15s!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " it tastes like feet!", "answer": " i like it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " are you kidding?", "answer": " what&#146;s not to like? custard? good. jam? good. meat? goooooood.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " the fridge broke. i have to eat everything. cold cuts, ice cream, limes&#151;hey, what was in that brown jar?", "answer": " that&#146;s still in there?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " oh! yay! look! there&#146;s a piece that doesn&#146;t have floor on", "answer": " stick to your side!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " uhh, i don&#146;t believe in these crazy diets y&#146;know, just everything in moderation.", "answer": " your muffins.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " i&#146;ll take those to go.  for the kids.", "answer": " oh, i know what i wanted to ask you. you were on the show years ago and then they killed you off. what happened there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " it was so stupid, i said some stuff in an interview that i shouldn&#146;t have said. but believe me, that&#146;s not gonna happen today.", "answer": " understood. so, what&#146;d you say back then?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " you guys, this is shelley, she&#146;s interviewing me for soap opera digest, and shelley, this are my friends&#133;", "answer": "  hi! i&#146;m gal pal rachel green, and if you want the dirt, i&#146;m the one you come too. this might be joey&#146;s baby , who knows? i&#146;m just kidding&#151;seriously,  gal pal rachel green.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  who just lost the respect of her unborn child.", "answer": " umm, i&#146;m gonna just go get this warmed up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " joey! you&#146;re doing great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " yeah, so far nothing stupid.", "answer": " mento?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " no thanks.", "answer": "  so, as joey&#146;s friends, is there anything that you guys think our readers ought to know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " uh no, no just-just that he is a great guy.", "answer": "  yeah, that&#146;s gonna get you into soap opera digest. well i&#133;&#133;i would just like to say that joey truly has enriched the days of our lives.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " umm, i&#133;i just think you don&#146;t expect someone so hot to be so sweet.", "answer": " oh! i like that. what&#146;s your name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " umm, phoebe buffay.", "answer": " how do you spell that? so we can get it right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " oh okay, it&#146;s p as in phoebe, h as in hoebe, o as in oebe, e as in ebe, b as in bee-bee and e as in  &#145;ello there mate!", "answer": " great! well, it was nice meeting all of you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " yeah, you too.", "answer": " you too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " how come you have two?", "answer": " well this one's for you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " get out.", "answer": " no, i can't. no-no, listen, i, i know how much this means to you and i also know that this is about more than just jewelry,  it's about you and me and the fact that we're  best buds.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " wow, is this friendship? i think so. check it out, we're bracelet buddies.", "answer": " that's what they'll call us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " oh, joey! sorry!", "answer": " no that&#146;s all right. don&#146;t worry about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " oh but look! that&#146;s gonna leave a stain!", "answer": " rach! hey! it&#146;s fine! you&#146;re at joey&#146;s!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah! look!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i&#146;ve never lived like this before.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " all right i've been feeling incredibly guilty about this, because i wanna be a good friend, and damnit i am a good friend. so just, just shut up and close your eyes .", "answer": " wow, you are a good friend, 'course the audition was this morning, and i didn't get it. but that was a hell of a kiss. rachel is a very lucky girl.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " get your foot off my contestant! judge!", "answer": " judge rules, no violation.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " ohhh.", "answer": " and the duck gets the nutter-butter!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  no!! hey-hey that's not a nutter-butter, that's just an old wonton!", "answer": " judge rules, nutter-butter.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " ohh, tough call.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " i&#146;d seen this thing on the discovery channel...", "answer": " wait a minute! i saw that! on the discovery channel, yeah! about jellyfish and how if you...  ewwww!! you peed on yourself?! phoebe and rachel: ewwww!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " you can&#146;t say that!! you-you don&#146;t know!! i mean i thought i was gonna pass out from the pain! anyway i-i tried, but i-i couldn&#146;t...bend that way. so...  phoebe, ross, and rachel:  ewwww!!", "answer": " that&#146;s right i stepped up! she&#146;s my friend and she needed help! and if i had too, i&#146;d pee on anyone of you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " umm, no. no best friend, no. just a lot of close friends.", "answer": " so umm, now back to the show. how does it feel to have a huge gay fan base?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what? are you referring to my man's bag? at first, i thought it just looked good, but it's practical too. check it out! it's got compartments for all your stuff! your wallet! your keys! your address book!", "answer": " your make-up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " okay. now-now-now should i climb down your front so we&#146;re face to face or-or should i climb down your back so we&#146;re-we&#146;re butt to face.", "answer": " i think face to face.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i would say that.", "answer": " face to face, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " okay, here i go.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  oh my&#133; how much do you weigh ross?!", "answer": " i prefer not to answer that right now, i&#146;m still carrying a little holiday weight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " check it out.  how much of a man am i?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " you&#146;re turning into a woman.", "answer": " no i&#146;m not. why would you say that? that&#146;s just mean.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " now i&#146;ve upset you? what did i say?", "answer": " it&#146;s not what you said. it&#146;s the way you said it&#133; oh my god, i&#146;m a woman!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " great nap.", "answer": " it really was.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " oh-oh-oh-oh, how i do it is, i look a woman up and down and say, &quot;hey, how you doin&#146;?&quot;", "answer": " oh, please!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " hey! how you doin&#146;?", "answer": "  he has the most amazing porsche under there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " hi, is rachel here? i&#146;m her sister.", "answer": " oh my god, jill!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " oh my god, introduce us!", "answer": " this is chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " and you know monica and ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " hi jill.", "answer": " and that&#146;s phoebe , and that&#146;s joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " hey,  how you doin&#146;?", "answer": " don&#146;t!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " no! i mean you're a really nice guy and i'm happy to be your roommate and your friend, i'm just y'know, i just don't feel that way about you.", "answer": " oh! i see what happened. it's because i was trying to repel you. right? believe me, you'd feel a lot different if i turned it on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " i don't think so.", "answer": " oh, i do.  how you doin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " i'm okay.", "answer": " what?!?! oh dear god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " so, that&#146;s it. i guess that&#146;s all i need. thank you so much. i think they will be running this in the beginning of next month.", "answer": " oh great! great! thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " bye.", "answer": " bye-bye.  i did it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " amazing! amazing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": "  oh wait! i almost forgot. we have to ask everybody this. other than days of our lives, what&#146;s your favorite soap opera?", "answer": " oh, i don&#146;t watch soap operas. excuse me, i have a life, y&#146;know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " thank you. the readers at soap opera digest will be happy to hear that.", "answer": " oh, good to know.  so close!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " wow! i can&#146;t believe they didn&#146;t put it in the part where you said you didn&#146;t watch soap operas.", "answer": " yeah, i called the lady about that. i told her i was just joking. she was pretty nice about that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " you slept with her didn&#146;t you?", "answer": " little bit, yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " wow! this picture of you sure is steamy.", "answer": " oh yeah, that&#146;s just a little something for my huge gay fan base.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " did you just wink at me?", "answer": " hey, you&#146;re the one that loves the picture.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep19.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}]